dollsofindia.com 2012-06-29

# Indian Art Store : Privacy Policy

DollsOfIndia is committed to respecting and protecting your personal privacy. Our Privacy Policy and your control over the information you provide us is outlined below.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM YOU OR YOUR COMPUTER**

  * You can visit our site and use many of our services without having to tell us who you are or reveal any personally identifiable information to us. It is only when you buy items from our site, make specific queries from us or leave reviews for items or articles on our website, through our website or through direct emails to any e-mail address, ending with @dollsofindia.com, that you will be asked to provide us with personally identifiable information.
  * Whenever you visit DollsOfIndia, our web server logs automatically receive and record anonymous information from your web browser including your IP Address, Referring page, the DollsOfIndia page(s) you request, and any search terms you query in our site.
  * DollsOfIndia uses this anonymous information to customize your experience on our site, maintain computer-specific shopping carts and to improve our services. We ordinarily do not attempt to link this information to a specific person, with certain important exceptions.
  * By providing us with personally identifiable information, you agree to receive communication from our end, which may or may not be limited to the resolution of a query posed by you. Please take a look at the "INFORMATION REMOVAL OR UPDATION" section below for asking us to remove you from our mailing/services database. 
  * DollsOfIndia uses personally identifiable information for three main purposes: to fulfill your orders for our products, to tell you about special offers and new products and services, and to send you articles of cultural interest.

**INFORMATION REMOVAL OR UPDATION**

  * Users, whose email/contact information are with us, may choose not to receive any future mailings/services from us by either visiting <http://www.dollsofindia.com/unsubscribe.php> or by writing to [**unsubscribe@dollsofindia.com**](mailto:unsubscribe@dollsofindia.com). You may also contact us at our address or phone number provided below. By writing in to us you can:
    * Request us to remove any personally identifiable information with us. This also implies that there cannot be any form of checking from our side to any future subscriptions to our services/mailings to contact addresses (physical or email) which points to you.
    * Request us to block any future mailings to your contact addresses (physical or email).
  * Users, whose email/contact information are with us, may choose to update their contact information with us by writing to [**info@dollsofindia.com**](mailto:info@dollsofindia.com). You may also contact us at our address or phone number provided below.

**PRIVACY OF INFORMATION**

  * DollsOfIndia will not share personally identifiable information with other companies or individuals unless:
    * We have your express permission to share the information
    * We need to share your information with any of our partner companies/individuals in order to provide a product or service that you have requested. Unless we tell you otherwise, these partners do not have the right to use your personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary to deliver your requested product or service
    * We comply with subpoenas or court orders
  * Except as we've just explained above, DollsOfIndia will not sell or disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone.

**INFORMATION SECURITY**
* DollsOfIndia has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.
* DollsOfIndia and its partner electronic payment gateway collects all financial information required for Billing in a 128 bit **SSL Secure Environment**.
**PRIVACY POLICY MODIFICATIONS**
* DollsOfIndia may modify its privacy policy from time to time. The responsibility of updating your knowledge about the same rests with you and the same can be done by visiting this page at regular intervals.
**DOLLSOFINDIA CONTACT INFORMATION REGARDING CONCERNS**
* To request for unsubscription OR removal from our customer database: [**unsubscribe@dollsofindia.com**](mailto:unsubscribe@dollsofindia.com)
* To request for modification or updation of customer information: [**info@dollsofindia.com**](mailto:info@dollsofindia.com)
* To request for clarifications on our privacy policy: [**info@dollsofindia.com**](mailto:info@dollsofindia.com)
* You may write to our physical address with any of the requests above. Write to:  
**Madhuri Guin  
P3B-085, Princeton Estate  
DLF City Phase V  
Gurgaon  
Haryana 122 009  
INDIA**
* You may contact us on our phone number : **+91-9810045075**.

## Library Archives

[Click here](http://www.dollsofindia.com/library/) **for list of archives**

According to Hindu philosophy, the world is made up of four main "Yugas" - ages, epochs or cycles of time - each made up of tens of thousands of human years... Each of these four Yugas involves stages of change; of evolution; one in which not only the physical universe undergoes change, but the whole thought process and consciousness of mankind metamorphoses either for better or for worse, depending upon that particular Yuga... Kalachakra puts us through repeated cycles of joy and suffering, depending upon our individual levels of karma... when one cycle of creation ends, God withdraws all of his energies into himself and rests for a period of time, when he is utterly inactive. After this period of rest, God resumes his activity and begins to recreate a whole new world, manifesting himself in an infinite number of new living beings and life forms...

## Testimonials

I received my order last week and wanted to say thank you. The packaging was excellent, and the jewelry set was more attractive than I had expected. Thank you for your prompt and most efficient...

Vineeta Sharma

I received my order and it's fantastic. Thank you very much for making this so easy.

evan mager

#### [Random Art Pages](http://www.dollsofindia.com/allpages.htm): [Nitai Gaur](http://www.dollsofindia.com/read/nitai-gaur.htm) - [Musician Ganesha Sculpture](http://www.dollsofindia.com/read/musician-ganesha-sculpture.htm) - [Lakshmi Statue](http://www.dollsofindia.com/read/lakshmi-statue.htm) - [Indian Classical Dances](http://www.dollsofindia.com/read/indian-classical-dances.htm) - [Woman Statues](http://www.dollsofindia.com/read/woman-statues.htm) - [Lovers Of India](http://www.dollsofindia.com/read/lovers-of-india.htm) - [Patchwork Bag](http://www.dollsofindia.com/read/patchwork-bag.htm) - [Indian Costume Jewelry](http://www.dollsofindia.com/read/indian-costume-jewelry.htm) - [Ganesha Picture](http://www.dollsofindia.com/read/ganesha-picture.htm) - [Ashtha Vinayaka](http://www.dollsofindia.com/read/ashtha-vinayaka.htm) 

**Copyright © 2012,[Dolls Of India](http://www.dollsofindia.com/)  
Site designed and maintained by [UnlimitedFX](http://www.unlimitedfx.com/)**
